<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Delivering a Workshop - Overview on Kubernetes Training</title>
    <link>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Delivering a Workshop - Overview on Kubernetes Training</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Students Prerequisite</title>
      <link>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/prereq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/prereq/</guid>
      <description>Creating a free IKS clusters In this section, you will learn how to create your free IBM Cloud Kubernetes Service (IKS) Cluster. This cluster will be a Managed cluster in the IBM Cloud Pak for Multicloud Management Workshop. In IBM Cloud, you can have 1 free cluster at a time in IBM Cloud Kubernetes Service, and each free cluster expires in 30 days. Free clusters have select capabilities, minimal 2x4 compute resources, select single zone locations, and support only the Kubernetes container platform and IBM Cloud classic infrastructure provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment Preparation</title>
      <link>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/preparation/</guid>
      <description>Installing CLI Tools CLI tools provide the ability to manage applications, containers, infrastructures, services, and other resources. In this section you will install all the necessary CLI tool in your local machine to be able to complete the Labs.
Note: If you have already installed all CLIs in your local machine, you can skip this page.
1.You should be on your CP4MCM Web Console, if not, check how to access it in Before Start page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WiaB - Multicluster Management</title>
      <link>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/clustermgmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/clustermgmt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;FeatureCard title=&amp;quot;WiaB - Multicluster Management with IBM Cloud Pak for Multicloud Management&amp;rdquo; color=&amp;quot;dark&amp;rdquo;
   Multicluster Management Overview  Lab Overview IBM Cloud Pak for Multicloud Management provides consistent visibility, automation, and governance across a range of multicloud management capabilities such as cost and asset management, infrastructure management, application management, multi-cluster management, edge management, and integration with existing tools and processes. Customers can leverage Cloud Pak for Multicloud Management to simplify their IT and application ops management, while increasing flexibility and cost savings with intelligent data analysis driven by predictive signals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WiaB Lab - Application Management</title>
      <link>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/appmgmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/appmgmt/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;FeatureCard title=&amp;quot;Application Management with IBM Cloud Pak for Multicloud Management&amp;rdquo; color=&amp;quot;dark&amp;rdquo;
   Lab Overview IBM Cloud Pak for Multicloud Management provides consistent visibility, automation, and governance across a range of multicloud management capabilities such as cost and asset management, infrastructure management, application management, multi-cluster management, edge management, and integration with existing tools and processes. Customers can leverage Cloud Pak for Multicloud Management to simplify their IT and application ops management, while increasing flexibility and cost savings with intelligent data analysis driven by predictive signals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivering a Workshop - Overview</title>
      <link>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://niklaushirt.github.io/k8s_training_web/workshop/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>